Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of theatrical productions at the Yale Rep and Yale School of Drama, 1970-1992; Accession 2008-A-004
  - Bosoms and Neglect, 1979-1980
    - Opening (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - They are Dying Out, 1979-1980
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Measure for Measure, 1979-1980
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Research (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Reviews-Features
  - Curse of the Starving Class, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Opening (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Research (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Ubo Rex, 1979-1980
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Lessons from Aloes, 1979-1980
  - Research (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Programs (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Memos-Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Boseman and Lena, 1980-1981
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Research (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - The Suicide, 1980-1981
    - Opening (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Twelfth Night, 1980-1981
    - Opening (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Hedda Gabler, 1980-1981
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Magnificent Cuckold, 1980-1981
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - An Attempt at Flying, 1980-1981
    - Research (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Winterfest 11, 1990-1991
    - Opening (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Research (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Programs (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 8, Folder 169)
    - Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 170)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - Winterfest 12, 1991-1992
    - Reviews-Features (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - Programs (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Fefu and Her Friends, 1991-1992
    - Reviews-Features (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - The Death of the Last Black Man in the Whole Entire World, 1991-1992
    - Reviews-Features (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Democracy in America, 1991-1992
    - Reviews-Features (Box 8, Folder 176)
    - Research (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Winterfest 10: Daylight in Exile, Pill Hill, Rust and Ruin and Dinosaurs, 1989-1990
    - Opening (Box 8, Folder 178)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 8, Folder 179)
    - Programs (Box 8, Folder 180)
    - Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 181)
    - Marketing (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Winterfest I: Domestic Issues, The Resurrections of Lady Lester, Rococo and Sally and Marsha, 1980-1981
    - Programs (Box 9, Folder 184)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - Winterfest 2: Beef, No Chicken, The Man Who Could See Through Time, 1981-1982
    - Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 186)
    - Programs (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - Winterfest 3: Axtapovo, Coyote Ugly, Playing in Local Bands, 1982-1983
    - Programs (Box 9, Folder 189)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 9, Folder 190)
    - Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 191)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - Winterfest 4: Chopin in Space, The Day of the Picnic, The Sweet Life Opening, 1983-1984
    - Opening (Box 9, Folder 193)
    - Programs (Box 9, Folder 194)
    - Study Guide (Box 9, Folder 195)
    - Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 196)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 9, Folder 197)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 198)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Winterfest 5: Between East and West, Faulkner's Bicycle, Rum and Coke, Vampires in Kodachrome, 1984-1985
    - Opening (Box 9, Folder 200)
    - Programs (Box 9, Folder 201)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 9, Folder 202)
    - Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 203)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 204)
  - Winterfest 6: A Child's Tale, Crazy from the Heart, Stitchers and Starlight Talkers, Union Boys, 1985-1986
    - Opening (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - Programs (Box 10, Folder 206)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - Newsletter (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - Study Guide (Box 10, Folder 209)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 210)
    - Marketing (Box 10, Folder 211)
  - Winterfest 7: Apocalyptic Butterflies, The Cometary Club, Exact Change, The Memento, 1986-1987
    - Opening (Box 10, Folder 212)
    - Programs (Box 10, Folder 213)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 10, Folder 214)
    - Newsletter (Box 10, Folder 215)
    - Marketing (Box 10, Folder 216)
  - Winterfest 8: Chute Roosters, Neddy, The My House Play, The Wall of Water, 1987-1988
    - Opening (Box 11, Folder 217)
    - Programs (Box 11, Folder 218)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 219)
    - Newsletter (Box 11, Folder 220)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 11, Folder 221)
    - Marketing (Box 11, Folder 222)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 223)
    - Ads (Box 11, Folder 224)
  - Winterfest 9: Phaedra and Hippolytus, The Beach, Starting Monday and Interrogating the Nude, 1988-1989
    - Opening (Box 11, Folder 225)
    - Newsletter (Box 11, Folder 226)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 227)
    - Programs (Box 11, Folder 228)
    - Ads (Box 11, Folder 229)
    - Marketing (Box 11, Folder 230)
  - Timon of Athens, 1979-1980
    - Reviews-Features (Box 12, Folder 231)
    - Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 232)
    - Programs (Box 12, Folder 233)
  - Are you Now or Have You Ever Been, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 234)
  - As You Like It, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 235)
  - B. Beaver Animation, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 236)
  - Baal, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 237)
  - The Banquet Years, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 238)
  - Bingo, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 239)
  - The Bourgeois Gentleman, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 240)
  - A Break in the Skin, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - The Bundle, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 242)
  - Buried Child, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - The Dark Room, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - Don Juan, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - Dynamite Tonight, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Elizabet I, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - General Gorgeous, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - Georgraphy of A Horse Dreamer, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 249)
  - The Ghost Sonata, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 250)
  - Happy End, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 251)
  - The Idiots Karamazov, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 252)
  - In the Clap Shack, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 253)
  - Ivanov, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 254)
  - Jacques Brel, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 255)
  - Julius Caesar, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 256)
  - Lear, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 257)
  - Macbett, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 258)
  - Macbeth, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 259)
  - Mahagonny, a Chamber Version of the Rise and Fall of the City of the Mahagonny, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 260)
  - Man is Man, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 261)
  - The Mirror, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 262)
  - Mistaken Identities, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 263)
  - The Possessed, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 265)
  - The 1940s Radio Hour, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 266)
  - The Rise and Fall of the City of Mahagonny, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 267)
  - The Revenger's Tragedy, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 268)
  - The SeaGull, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 269)
  - Sganarelle, An Evening of Moliere Farces, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 270)
  - The Shaft of Love, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 271)
  - Shlemiel the first, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 272)
  - Suicide in B-Flat, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 273)
  - Tales from the Vienna Woods, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 274)
  - The Tempest, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 275)
  - Terra Nova, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 276)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 277)
  - The Tubs, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 278)
  - Story Theatre IV: Joseph Conrad's Victory, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 279)
  - The Vietnamization of New Jersey An American Tragedy, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 280)
  - Watergate Classics, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 282)
  - Where Has Tommy Flowers Gone?, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - White Marriage, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 284)
  - The Wild Duck, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 285)
  - Wings, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 286)
  - The Miser, 1987-1988
    - Opening (Box 15, Folder 288)
    - Programs (Box 15, Folder 289)
    - Newsletter (Box 15, Folder 290)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 15, Folder 291)
    - Study Guide (Box 15, Folder 292)
    - Marketing (Box 15, Folder 293)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 294)
  - Long Days Journey Into Night, 1987-1988
    - Opening (Box 15, Folder 295)
    - Research (Box 15, Folder 296)
    - Programs (Box 15, Folder 297)
    - Newsletter (Box 15, Folder 298)
    - Study Guide (Box 15, Folder 299)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 15, Folder 300)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 301)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 302)
  - Ah Wilderness, 1987-1988
    - Opening (Box 16, Folder 303)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 16, Folder 304)
    - Marketing (Box 16, Folder 305)
    - Study Guide (Box 16, Folder 306)
  - Intermezzo, 1988-1989
    - Opening (Box 16, Folder 307)
    - Programs (Box 16, Folder 308)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 16, Folder 309)
    - Newsletter (Box 16, Folder 310)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 311)
    - Marketing (Box 16, Folder 312)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman, 1988-1989
    - Reviews-Features (Box 16, Folder 313)
    - Programs (Box 16, Folder 314)
    - Newsletter (Box 16, Folder 315)
    - Study Guide (Box 16, Folder 316)
    - Marketing (Box 16, Folder 317)
  - The Alchemist, 1988-1989
    - Opening (Box 17, Folder 318)
    - Programs (Box 17, Folder 319)
    - Study Guide (Box 17, Folder 320)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 17, Folder 321)
    - Marketing (Box 17, Folder 322)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 323)
    - Newsletter (Box 17, Folder 324)
  - Moon Over Miami, 1988-1989
    - Opening (Box 17, Folder 325)
    - Programs (Box 17, Folder 326)
    - Study Guide (Box 17, Folder 327)
    - Newsletter (Box 17, Folder 328)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 17, Folder 329)
  - Cobb, 1988-1989
    - Opening (Box 17, Folder 330)
    - Programs (Box 17, Folder 331)
    - Newsletter (Box 17, Folder 332)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 17, Folder 333)
    - Marketing (Box 17, Folder 334)
    - Study Guide (Box 17, Folder 335)
  - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1989
    - Opening (Box 18, Folder 336)
    - Research (Box 18, Folder 337)
    - Programs (Box 18, Folder 338)
    - Study Guide (Box 18, Folder 339)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 18, Folder 340)
    - Newsletter (Box 18, Folder 341)
    - Marketing (Box 18, Folder 342)
  - The Warrior Ant, 1988-1989
    - Programs (Box 18, Folder 343)
    - Newsletter (Box 18, Folder 344)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 18, Folder 345)
    - Marketing (Box 18, Folder 346)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 347)
  - The Solid Gold Cadillac, 1989-1990
    - Opening (Box 18, Folder 348)
    - Programs (Box 18, Folder 349)
    - Newsletter (Box 18, Folder 350)
    - Marketing (Box 18, Folder 351)
  - Miss Julie, 1989-1990
    - Opening (Box 19, Folder 352)
    - Programs (Box 19, Folder 353)
    - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 354)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 19, Folder 355)
    - Study Guide (Box 19, Folder 356)
  - Summer and Smoke, 1989-1990
    - Opening (Box 19, Folder 357)
    - Programs (Box 19, Folder 358)
    - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 359)
    - Study Guide (Box 19, Folder 360)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 19, Folder 361)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1989-1990
    - Opening (Box 19, Folder 362)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 19, Folder 363)
    - Programs (Box 19, Folder 364)
    - Study Guide (Box 19, Folder 365)
    - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 366)
  - Pygmalion, 1989-1990
    - Opening (Box 19, Folder 367)
    - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 368)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 19, Folder 369)
    - Study Guide (Box 19, Folder 370)
    - Programs (Box 19, Folder 371)
  - Two Trains Running, 1989-1990
    - Tony Nomination Clips (Box 20, Folder 372)
    - Newsletter (Box 20, Folder 373)
    - Programs (Box 20, Folder 374)
    - Marketing (Box 20, Folder 375)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 20, Folder 376)
  - Ivanov, 1990-1991
    - Opening (Box 20, Folder 377)
    - Programs (Box 20, Folder 378)
    - Research (Box 20, Folder 379)
    - Newsletter (Box 20, Folder 380)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 20, Folder 381)
    - Study Guide (Box 20, Folder 382)
  - Large Desolato, 1990-1991
    - Opening (Box 20, Folder 383)
    - Research (Box 20, Folder 384)
    - Programs (Box 20, Folder 385)
  - Search and Destroy, 1990-1991
    - Opening (Box 20, Folder 386)
    - Programs (Box 20, Folder 387)
    - Newsletter (Box 20, Folder 388)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 20, Folder 389)
    - Study Guide (Box 20, Folder 390)
  - Underground, 1990-1991
    - Opening (Box 21, Folder 391)
    - Research (Box 21, Folder 392)
    - Study Guide (Box 21, Folder 393)
    - Newsletter (Box 21, Folder 394)
    - Programs (Box 21, Folder 395)
    - Reviews-Feature (Box 21, Folder 396)
  - Scapin, 1990-1991
    - Opening (Box 21, Folder 397)
    - Study Guide (Box 21, Folder 398)
    - Programs (Box 21, Folder 399)
    - Newsletter (Box 21, Folder 400)
    - Reviews-Feature (Box 21, Folder 401)
    - Research (Box 21, Folder 402)
  - A Moon for the Misbegotten, 1990-1991
    - Opening (Box 21, Folder 403)
    - Study Guide (Box 21, Folder 404)
    - Programs (Box 21, Folder 405)
    - Newsletter (Box 21, Folder 406)
    - Reviews-Feature (Box 21, Folder 407)
  - Sarcophagus, 1987-1988
    - Opening (Box 21, Folder 408)
    - Programs (Box 21, Folder 409)
    - Reviews-Feature (Box 21, Folder 410)
    - Newsletter (Box 21, Folder 411)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 412)
    - Marketing (Box 21, Folder 413)
  - Melons, 1987-1988
    - Opening (Box 22, Folder 414)
    - Programs (Box 22, Folder 415)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 22, Folder 416)
    - Newsletter (Box 22, Folder 417)
  - The Piano Lesson, 1987-1988
    - Opening (Box 22, Folder 418)
    - Newsletter (Box 22, Folder 419)
    - National Tour (Box 22, Folder 420)
    - Programs (Box 22, Folder 421)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 22, Folder 422)
    - Marketing (Box 22, Folder 423)
    - Study Guide (Box 22, Folder 424)
  - Heartbreak House, 1986-1987
    - Opening (Box 23, Folder 425)
    - Programs (Box 23, Folder 426)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 23, Folder 427)
    - Newsletter (Box 23, Folder 428)
    - Study Guide (Box 23, Folder 429)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 430)
    - Marketing (Box 23, Folder 431)
  - Neapolitan Ghosts, 1986-1987
    - Opening (Box 23, Folder 432)
    - Programs (Box 23, Folder 433)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 23, Folder 434)
    - Study Guide (Box 23, Folder 435)
    - Marketing (Box 23, Folder 436)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1986-1987
    - Opening (Box 23, Folder 437)
    - Marketing (Box 23, Folder 438)
    - Programs (Box 23, Folder 439)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 23, Folder 440)
    - Newsletter (Box 23, Folder 441)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 442)
  - A Place with the Pigs, 1986-1987
    - Opening (Box 23, Folder 443)
    - Research (Box 23, Folder 444)
    - Programs (Box 23, Folder 445)
    - Newsletter (Box 23, Folder 446)
    - Study Guide (Box 23, Folder 447)
    - M (Box 23, Folder 448)
  - Elizabeth, 1986-1987
    - Opening (Box 23, Folder 449)
    - Programs (Box 23, Folder 450)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 23, Folder 451)
    - Newsletter (Box 23, Folder 452)
    - Study Guide (Box 23, Folder 453)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 454)
  - A Walk in the Woods, 1987-1988
    - Opening (Box 24, Folder 455)
    - Programs (Box 24, Folder 456)
    - La Jolla (Box 24, Folder 457)
    - Booth (Box 24, Folder 458)
    - Library of Congress (Box 24, Folder 459)
    - Vaktangof (Box 24, Folder 460)
    - Comedy (Box 24, Folder 461)
    - Program in Russian (Box 24, Folder 462)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 24, Folder 463)
    - Newsletter (Box 24, Folder 464)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 465)
    - Marketing (Box 24, Folder 466)
    - Broadway (Box 24, Folder 467)
    - Duke (Box 24, Folder 468)
  - Blood Knot, 1985-1986
    - Reviews-Features (Box 24, Folder 469)
    - Programs (Box 24, Folder 470)
    - Study Guide (Box 24, Folder 471)
    - Memos-Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 472)
    - Notes (Box 24, Folder 473)
  - Marriage, 1985-1986
    - Opening (Box 25, Folder 474)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 25, Folder 475)
    - Newsletter (Box 25, Folder 476)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 477)
    - Marketing (Box 25, Folder 478)
  - Othello, 1985-1986
    - Opening (Box 25, Folder 479)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 25, Folder 480)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 481)
  - Importance of Being Earnest, 1985-1986
    - Opening (Box 25, Folder 482)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 25, Folder 483)
    - Programs (Box 25, Folder 484)
    - Study Guide (Box 25, Folder 485)
    - Marketing (Box 25, Folder 486)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 487)
  - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, 1985-1986
    - Opening (Box 25, Folder 488)
    - Programs (Box 25, Folder 489)
    - Reviews-Features (Box 25, Folder 490)
    - Marketing (Box 25, Folder 491)
    - Arena Stage (Box 25, Folder 492)
    - Broadway (Box 25, Folder 493)
    - Huntington (Box 25, Folder 494)
    - Old Globe (Box 25, Folder 495)
  - Little Eyolf, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 496)
- School of Drama records, 1926-2002; Accession 2008-A-106; 5.25; (5 boxes)
  - Yale School of Drama Posters, 1926-1927 production assignment chart, 1926, 1960-1996 (Box 1)
  - Publicity packets, 1956-1988 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1931-1964 (Box 4)
  - Flyers and programs, 1951-1995 (Box 5)
- School of Drama Student Government records, 1997-2008; 1997-1998; Accession 2016-A-017
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2043 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
  - Planning documents, meeting notes and event memorabilia, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Meeting agendas, budgets, governance documents and calendars, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)